ANDRÉS PÉREZ GUARDIOLA

CONTACT

Esparza, Puntarenas

+506 86539639

andres.pguardiola@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native

English Advanced

SKILLS

- Bootstrap
- Vue.js
- React
- React Native
- SASS
- Laravel
- Wordpress
- Figma
- MySQL
- Firebase
- Linux
- Drupal
- GitHub

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable Web Developer incorporates solid technical bases with creative user interface design. Combines aesthetic considerations with technical expertise to produce visually attractive and highly functional sites and apps. Committed to providing visitors with smooth and pleasant interactions.

EXPERIENCE

Find Ur House

• July 2022 - August 2022

Web Developer

- Developed websites to work properly across Microsoft, Google and Mozilla browsers.
- Created error-free code in HTML, Java and PHP.
- Used coding skills to build prototype sites according to designer vision.
- Checked web pages for compatibility with the browsers, devices and operating systems commonly
 used by customers.

Geek News

March 2022 - July 2022

Web Developer

- Collaborated with design team to create attractive and user-friendly websites.
- Created error-free code in HTML, Java and PHP.
- Worked on back end to develop server logic protocols and manage database connections.
- Improved coding of JavaScript and CSS to enhance user experience and functionality.

UpTask

August 2022 - December 2022

Android Developer

- Prototyped new innovative features with latest APIs and SDKs for Android.
- Designed and developed innovative features improving application efficiency and performance.
- Researched and selected database architectures best suited to individual storage projects and needs.
- Verified database performance after updates to identify and correct inefficiencies.

EDUCATION

December 2023

Bachelor of Computer Science and Multimedia Technology Universidad de Costa Rica

January 2023

Professional Fundamentals of Software Development
Microsoft & LinkedIn

November 2022

Vue.js: From 0 to expert

Udemy

October 2022

Flutter: Your Complete Development Guide for IOS and Android

Udemy

January 2022

Complete Web Development with HTML5, CSS3, JS AJAX PHP and MySQL

Udemy

ANDRÉS PÉREZ GUARDIOLA

CONTACT

Esparza, Puntarenas

\$\\$\\$ +506 86539639

andres.pguardiola@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

Español Native

Ingles Advanced

SKILLS

- Bootstrap
- Vue.js
- React
- React Native
- SASS
- Laravel
- Wordpress
- Figma
- MySQL
- Firebase
- Linux
- Drupal
- GitHub

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Desarrollador web fiable que incorpora sólidas bases técnicas con un diseño creativo de la interfaz de usuario. Combina consideraciones estéticas con experiencia técnica para producir sitios y aplicaciones visualmente atractivos y altamente funcionales. Comprometido a ofrecer a los visitantes interacciones fluidas y agradables.

EXPERIENCE

Find Ur House

• July 2022 - August 2022

Desarrollador Web

- Desarrollo de sitios web que funcionen correctamente en los navegadores Microsoft, Google y Mozilla.
- Creación de código sin errores en HTML, Java y PHP.
- Utilización de conocimientos de codificación para crear prototipos de sitios web de acuerdo con la visión del diseñador.
- Comprobación de la compatibilidad de las páginas web con los navegadores, dispositivos y sistemas operativos más utilizados por los clientes.

Geek News

March 2022 - July 2022

Desarrollador Web

- Colaboración con el equipo de diseño para crear sitios web atractivos y fáciles de usar.
- Creación de código sin errores en HTML, Java y PHP.
- Trabajé en el back-end para desarrollar protocolos lógicos de servidor y gestionar conexiones de bases de datos.
- Mejora de la codificación de JavaScript y CSS para mejorar la experiencia del usuario y la funcionalidad.

UpTask

August 2022 - December 2022

Desarrollador Android

- Creación de prototipos de nuevas funciones innovadoras con las últimas API y SDK para Android.
- Diseño y desarrollo de funciones innovadoras para mejorar la eficacia y el rendimiento de las aplicaciones.
- Investigación y selección de las arquitecturas de bases de datos más adecuadas para cada proyecto y necesidad de almacenamiento.
- Verificación del rendimiento de la base de datos tras las actualizaciones para identificar y corregir ineficiencias.

EDUCATION

December 2023

Bachillerato en Informática y Tecnología Multimedia Universidad de Costa Rica

January 2023

Fundamentos Profesionales en Desarrollo de Software Microsoft & LinkedIn

November 2022

Vue.js: De 0 a Experto

Udemy

October 2022

Flutter: Tu Guía Completa de Desarrollo en IOS y Android Udemy

January 2022

Desarrollo Web Completo con HTML5, CSS3, JS AJAX PHP y MySQL Udemy